<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>dev.IL engineering</title>
    <link>//devil-engineering.de/</link>
    <description>Recent content on dev.IL engineering</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="//devil-engineering.de/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>//devil-engineering.de/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 20:50:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//devil-engineering.de/contact/</guid>
      <description> Full Name Email address Your Message SUBMIT </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience</title>
      <link>//devil-engineering.de/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 20:50:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//devil-engineering.de/experience/</guid>
      <description>Freelancer Senior .NET Consultant, MCITP, MCTS, SCRUM Master location: worldwide since: 14 years 9 months 2023 EnBW (Energie Baden-Württemberg AG) architecture, requirements-engineering and devops of a event-driven integration platform location: Cologne / Karlsruhe, Germany since: 4 years 2023 Parental Leave Japan, South-Korea, United Arab Emirates, South-Africa duration: 1 year 2019 EnBW (Energie Baden-Württemberg AG) Cologne / Karlsruhe, Germany duration: 3 years 9 months 2018 EAS Engineering Automation Systems GmbH Kirchhundem, Germany duration: 6 months 2014 Elster GmbH / Kromschröder Osnabrück, Germany duration: 3 months 2014 Stadtsparkasse Düsseldorf Düsseldorf, Germany duration: 6 months 2014 Tengelmann Energie GmbH Mülheim an der Ruhr, Germany duration: 1 month 2014 EAS Engineering Automation Systems GmbH Kirchhundem, Germany duration: 4 months 2014 Saphir Software GmbH Leverkusen, Germany duration: 3 months 2013 Able Management Services GmbH Gummersbach, Germany duration: 1 month 2013 Jenoptik GmbH Mohnheim, Germany / Muscat, Oman duration: 11 months 2013 Jenoptik Robot Malaysia Sdn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legal Disclosure</title>
      <link>//devil-engineering.de/legal-disclosure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 20:50:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//devil-engineering.de/legal-disclosure/</guid>
      <description>Information according to § 5 TMG (German Telemedia Act) Link to heading Marcus Kimpenhaus
Höhmanns Siepen 10
D-44795 Bochum
Deutschland
Contact: Link to heading telephon: +49 (0)171 - 4914407
email: legal-disclosure@devil-engineering.de
Responsible for the content according to § 55(2) RStV (Interstate Broadcasting Treaty): Link to heading Marcus Kimpenhaus
Höhmanns Siepen 10
D-44795 Bochum
Deutschland
Disclaimer: Link to heading The information provided on this website is for general informational purposes only.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Philosophy</title>
      <link>//devil-engineering.de/philosophy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 20:50:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//devil-engineering.de/philosophy/</guid>
      <description>With over 20 years of experience in crafting and delivering enterprise-scale applications, I bring a wealth of knowledge and expertise to the table. As a freelance Cloud Engineer and DevOps specialist, I am dedicated to helping businesses leverage the power of modern technologies to achieve their goals efficiently and securely.
My philosophy revolves around the core principle of continuous improvement. I strongly believe that technology is ever-evolving, and staying ahead of the curve is essential to drive innovation and deliver exceptional results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>//devil-engineering.de/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 20:50:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//devil-engineering.de/publications/</guid>
      <description>Explore a collection of my top-notch plugins, extensions, and transformative talks I have provided to the community in the last copule of years.
Fake the Unfakeable Talk about Isolating Code Under Test with Microsoft Fakes©
Find slides here and modules on GitHub
2014 Was dir Trivialbeispiele in Async and Await nicht sagen! Talk about evolution of asynchronous development and patterns when using async/await
Find slides here and modules on GitHub</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skills</title>
      <link>//devil-engineering.de/skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 20:50:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//devil-engineering.de/skills/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
